

#### **PROFILE**

Almost 3 years of experience in the BPO industry and 4 years of experience in customer service. Committed to working hard keeping discipline, consistency, and teamwork to achieve goals and success. Currently, studying programming to combine both customer service and technological skills. You can find my GitHub profile by clicking on contact information. I would like to highlight the following quote:

"I'm the type of person that if you ask me a question and I don't know the answer, I'm gonna tell you that I don't know. But I bet you what, I know how to find the answer and I will find the answer."

#### CONTACT

## DOB:

09/25/1999

# Mobile Phone:

+57 (321) 310 16 15

#### e-mail:

davidsilvav6@gmail.com

#### LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidstiven-silva-velandia-ba3529236/

#### GitHub:

https://github.com/KaonyKampus

#### Address:

Colombia

# DAVID STIVEN SILVA VELANDIA

### **EDUCATION**

Fundación Universitaria Compensar | Degree in Software engineer 2023-Currently

**Coderhouse | Full stack programming** 2023 – Currently

Universidad ECCI | Degree in Modern Languages 2017 – 2022

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Asurion | Technical Support Agent

2022 - Currently

Technical support agent. Asist customer with technical support in terms of phones, tablets, computers and televisions.

# Teleperformance | Customer Service Agent

2021 - 2022

Customer service agent. Assisted customers from Walmart with different inquiries regarding packages and orders. Interactions via phone, email and chat.

# TuBici Bike Shop | Seller

2020 - 2020

Customer service person, seller and administrative assistant. Bicycles environment.